<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="xml-style.css"?>

<boat-tour-listings>

<!-- Empty listing 
<listing>
<name></name>
<image alt="" width="320" height="">boat-tours/</image>
<description>
</description>
<location></location>
<phone></phone>
<email></email>
<website></website>
<lat></lat>
<long></long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<!-- Category: Boat Tours -->

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Assateague Explorer Pony Watching Cruise</name>
<image alt="Assateague Explorer" width="211" height="246">boat-tours/assateague-explorer-ad.jpg</image>
<description>
"Where are the Wild Ponies?" Since 2001, the Pony Express Nature Cruise has provided the best opportunity to observe wild ponies along the boarders of Assateague's extensive calm western 
shoreline. Departs from the southern end of Chincoteague Island and spend more time along the best part of Assateague looking for wild ponies, dolphins, eagles, shorebirds and other 
wildlife. Enjoy a sunset wildlife cruise for a spectacular coastal experience or add a kayak tour for more adventurous experience. Cruise/kayak packages &amp; group/family discounts available. 
Be sure to call ahead for reservations. Featured on the ABC "Good Morning America" show, Coastal Living Magazine, Southern Living Magazine, Family Fun Magazine and more.  
</description>
<location>Curtis Merritt Harbor, Chincoteague</location>
<phone>1-866-PONY SWIM (toll free) or (757) 336-5956</phone>
<email>info@assateagueexplorer.com</email>
<website>http://www.assateagueexplorer.com/</website>
<lat>37.901878</lat>
<long>-75.406864</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Assateague Tours</name>
<image alt="Assateague Tours" width="225" height="220">boat-tours/assateague-tours-ad.jpg</image>
<description>
Assateague Tours offers the best Boat Tours and Kayak Tours along Chincoteague and Assateague Islands. We offer group tours as well as Private Exclusive Tours. We will take you to the most remote areas of the National Refuge for 
ponywatching and birdwatching. Assateague Boat and Kayak Tours will get you up close and personal with the wild Chincoteague ponies and all the wildlife Assateague Island has to offer. We offer morning tours, pony tours, nature 
tours and sunset crusies. Assateague Tours will tour the great marshlands of Chincoteague &amp; Assateague. We go around the islands to find the world famous Chincoteague ponies, dolphins and the biggest selection of native birds on 
the east coast. Just call us at 757-336-6176 to make a reservation or visit www.assateaguetours.com for more info.
</description>
<location>7512 East Side Road, Chincoteague</location>
<phone>757-336-6176</phone>
<email>snugharbor@verizon.net</email>
<website>http://www.assateaguetours.com/</website>
<lat>37.916979</lat>
<long>-75.374642</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/dWRFbUpeLM52</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Barnacle Bill's Boat Tours</name>
<image alt="Barnacle Bills Boat Tours" width="214" height="244">boat-tours/barnacle-bills-banner.jpg</image>
<description>
Come take a boat tour with Master Captain Barnacle Bill! Enjoy breath taking scenery as you sail the Chincoteague and Assateague Island waters in search of adventure and discovery. Amoung some of the things you will see are 
Bald Eagles, Wild Ponies, The Assateague Lighouse, Dolphin, a large veriaty of birds and waterfowl, and some of the most beautiful sunsets you will ever experiance. Because Bill and his family are from Chincoteague he can tell 
you many storys about life as it was years ago when his grandparents lived, worked, and even whent to school on Assateague. "I am Barnacle Bill, your Captain, born and raised in the same house that my dad was born and raised in 
on Chincoteague Island."</description>
<location>Curtis Merritt Harbor</location>
<phone>757-894-3745</phone>
<email></email>
<website>https://www.barnaclebillswildponyboattours.com/</website>
<lat>37.903159</lat>
<long>-75.405119</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/S9xisT5uLb82</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Captain Barry's Back Bay Cruises</name>
<image alt="Captain Barrys Back Bay Cruises" width="220" height="293">boat-tours/capt-barry-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Captain Barry's Back Bay Cruises is an interactive skill building experience. We are a floating classroom, a research vessel with hands-on, feet-wet lessons. One of the many things we do is get off the boat on the sandbars to go 
dig in the mud for sea creatures. Then its back on to cruise to a crabbing spot where you will pull crab pots on board to identify and see the day's catch. If you have the courage I'll teach you how to hold a crab without 
getting pinched. Navigating our way to Shell Island Beach, we stop and get off the boat for some shell collecting then back on the boat for Captain Barry's favorite activity... hunting for jellyfish! We will then haul in the 
trawler net with its abundance of marine life. Now its time to get a taste of Chincoteague, harvesting our famous salt oysters. Time to slow the boat down to enter the shallow waters... how many birds can you identify? We use 
all of our senses - sound, touch, taste and smell - to make our cruise informative and fun. There is never any pressure, always lots of fun... you can relax, sit back on the boat and be the official photographer, or you can get 
it. This is the real deal If you want to get your hands dirty and feet wet so you will experience the life of a true Chincoteague Waterman.
</description>
<location>6262 Marlin Street (next to the Fairfield Inn)</location>
<phone>757-336-6508</phone>
<email>captainchincoteague@gmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.captainbarry.net/</website>
<lat>37.933269</lat>
<long>-75.380073</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/o8WLJ18AvrF2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Captain Dan's Around the Island Cruises</name>
<image alt="Captain Dans Around the Island Cruises" width="225" height="162">boat-tours/captdans3.jpg</image>
<description>
Try our newly modified "Pony Tour" now available daily in the afternoons, search up to 21 miles of pony viewing coastline. Our “Pony Tour” finds ponies at a distance of less 
than 100 yards over 90% of the time. On our "Around the Island Tour" we search for ponies, dolphin, wild fowl, and other local sights. Travel over 25 total miles of unique 
coastline, never passing the same area twice, see it all! All trips are 2-3 hours, and include local history and commentary from your guide. Afternoon "Pony Tour" may be 
aboard our larger 14 passenger boat. All other trips aboard our 6 passenger pontoon boats. Groups of more than 6 inquire about a private tour aboard our larger boat. Board 
from the floating dock in the Downtown Park adjacent to Don's Seafood Restaurant.</description>
<location>Downtown park</location>
<phone>757-894-0103</phone>
<email>CaptainDan@CaptainDansTours.com</email>
<website>http://captdantours.premiumsitehosting.com/</website>
<lat>37.934559</lat>
<long>-75.377423</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/mBxJ7xHJQBU2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Chincoteague Island Adventures</name>
<image alt="Chincoteague Island Adventures" width="225" height="161">boat-tours/chincoteague-island-adventures.jpg</image>
<description>
Captain Randy Birch is a true "Teaguer" - he was born and raised on Chincoteague Island and for his whole life has made his living on and around the island. He is a waterman by trade, harvesting hard and softshell crabs, minnows 
and horseshoe crabs during the summer, and guiding waterfowl hunts in the winter. He knows the waters intimately and lends a unique authenticity to the tour experience. Captain Randy knows where the Wild Ponies live and he will 
take you to see them. Sunrise and sunset tours are recommended, other times are available upon request. Please visit his web site for more information.
</description>
<location>4436 Williams Lane, Chincoteague</location>
<phone>757-894-5964</phone>
<email>Chincoteagueislandadventures@yahoo.com</email>
<website>http://www.chincoteagueislandadventures.com/</website>
<lat>37.922469</lat>
<long>-75.363926</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/1U2xVueC8oG2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Daisey's Island Cruises</name>
<image alt="Daiseys Island Cruises" width="213" height="248">boat-tours/daiseys-cruises-banner8.jpg</image>
<description>
Cruise remote areas of Assateague Island with the life-long local guides of Daisey’s Island Cruises. Owner and Captain, Carlton Leonard, is a Chincoteague Island Native and been a waterman most of his life. Every tour is rich 
with history, humor and education on the wildlife and local landscape of Chincoteague and Assateague Island. We will take you to where the wild ponies live. Our scenic nature tours feature close-up views of the world-famous 
ponies, dolphins, bald eagles, and beautiful sunsets... all from our exceptionally comfortable pontoon boats. With tours limited to six passengers, there is always plenty of room to relax on the spacious sofas, while your Captain 
fills you in on all the local knowledge. Don’t miss what is sure to be the highlight of your Chincoteague vacation! Please check out our web site and read our customer testimonials. 
</description>
<location>3335 Main Street, Chincoteague (Daisey's Dockside Pier and Dockhouse)</location>
<phone>757-336-5556</phone>
<email>fun@daiseyscruises.com</email>
<website>http://www.daiseysislandcruises.com/</website>
<lat>37.919946</lat>
<long>-75.391928</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/WjJ2jByeto72</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Island Queen Inland Charters</name>
<image alt="Island Queen Inland Charters" width="229" height="159">boat-tours/islandqueen.jpg</image>
<description>
Chincoteague Island Inland Bay fishing for flounder, kingfish, croaker, bluefish, trout, or spot on board a 26 ft. Pontoon Boat. Species may vary during season.  All bait, fishing rod/tackle &amp; licenses supplied or bring your 
own. Captain experienced with over 30 years fishing the inland waters of Chincoteague Island. Children welcome and handicap access available. Scenic Cruises available also.
</description>
<location>Curtis Merritt Harbor - Slip 16</location>
<phone>757-336-3528 or 757-990-2404 cell</phone>
<email>ckoski2@verizon.net</email>
<website>http://www.islandqueeninlandcharters.com/</website>
<lat>37.901823</lat>
<long>-75.407066</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/nybCmBDLbvS2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Charter Boats">Light Tackle Charters, Inc.</name>
<image alt="Light Tackle Charters, Inc." width="228" height="189">boat-tours/LTC-Banner.jpg</image>
<description>
Over 45 Years "On The Water". A very seaworthy Parker 23' Center Console Boat with Yamaha 200HP Motor which can accommodate up to 
six (6) people. Offering <![CDATA[<u>exclusively</u>]]>, trips out of Crisfield Maryland <![CDATA[<u>only</u>]]> on the Chesapeake Bay side of the peninsula (only a 50 
minute drive from Chincoteague). Fish the middle Chesapeake Bay with Captain Walt where we catch Striped Bass, Speckled Trout, Red 
Drum, Bluefish and other species. Also offering trips to remote and quaint <![CDATA[<u>Tangier Island Virginia</u>]]> as well as 
<![CDATA[<u>Smith Island Maryland</u>]]>.
</description>
<location>543 Wellington Road, Crisfield, MD 21817</location>
<phone>410-845-3231</phone>
<email>CapnWalt@gmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.ltcharters.com/</website>
<lat>1234</lat>
<long>1234</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/zvzGsebTxyA2</gm_link>
</listing>
<!--
<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Marshland Charters</name>
<image alt="" width="230" height="161">boat-tours/marshland-charters.jpg</image>
<description>
Bay fishing or cruising the bays and coves around Chincoteague Island can make some great lasting memories for you and your family. Captain Matt is dedicated to helping you with these memories. We fish the bays and channels for 
flounder, croakers, blue fish, and many other species. We will also take you on a true back bay cruise. We go places no other cruise boats go to see birds on the flats, Ospreys on their nest, and Eagles. Dolphins can be seen 
feeding and playing. You may also get to walk on a sand bar and get sand in your toes!
</description>
<location>Curtis Merritt Harbor - Slip #85</location>
<phone>757-894-1627 or 757-894-1626</phone>
<email>marshlandcharters@verizon.net</email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/marshland-charters/</website>
<lat>37.903241</lat>
<long>-75.405973</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Proud Mary Charters</name>
<image alt="Proud Mary Charters" width="228" height="201">boat-tours/pm-charters.jpg</image>
<description>
THE PROUD MARY is a 24 foot BayRider skiff with plenty of room for six anglers or pleasure cruisers. Take a fishing charter with Captain George, or tour the surrounding area and go to the back bay to view nature. All bait and 
tackle is included. Just bring your snacks and beverages. Don't forget your sun screen, cameras and sun glasses. With no more than six passengers, sit back and enjoy your trip. The Proud Mary offers two hour and four hour trips. 
THE PROUD MARY TOO is a 19 foot Carolina Skiff. Join Captain Mary on a CUSTOM TOUR of the beautiful waters that surround the Island. Captain Mary will create an experience made just for you. Possibilities include a quest to find 
wild ponies and see dolphins in their natural habitat, pulling crab traps and bringing home your catch, or a private picnic on a sand bar. 
</description>
<location>Curtis Merritt Harbor - Slips 28 &amp; 48</location>
<phone>757-894-0771 or 757-894-9862 or 757-336-5931</phone>
<email>pmcharter@hotmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.chincoteaguecharters.com/</website>
<lat>37.902177</lat>
<long>-75.405807</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Saltwater Pony Tours</name>
<image alt="Saltwater Pony Tours" width="218" height="190">boat-tours/salt-water-pony-tours.jpg</image>
<description>
There are several choices for tours of Chincoteague and Assateague, but few that will get you as close to the 
Ponies and other wildlife as Captain Henry. We always travel all the way around Chincoteague Island and 
through the backwaters of Assateague Island to get the best possible view of the Chincoteague Ponies, Dolphin, 
Eagles, Osprey, and other wildlife that you came to the island to see. Our shallow draft vessel will navigate 
hard to reach areas to get you as close as possible to the action. Don’t take our word for it. We pride 
ourselves on the positive feedback that we consistently receive from Tripadvisor. Come see why we have 
consistently been awarded Tripadvisor's Certificate of Excellence year after year. 
<![CDATA[<a href="https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g57602-d3378459-Reviews-Saltwater_Pony_Tours-Chincoteague_Island_Virginia.html" target="_blank">]]>Click here<![CDATA[</a>]]> to read some of 
our customer reviews!
</description>
<location>Island Motor Inn Resort, 4391 Main Street, Chincoteague</location>
<phone>757-710-1783</phone>
<email>saltwaterponytours@hotmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.saltwaterponytours.com/</website>
<lat>37.939979</lat>
<long>-75.369825</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Boat Tours,Map View">Spider's Explorer</name>
<image alt="Spiders Explorer" width="212" height="248">boat-tours/spiders-explorer-banner.jpg</image>
<description>
Around the Island we go! Cruising April-October around Chincoteague and Assateague Islands.  Compliments abound from our customers who have experienced wild ponies, bald eagles, dolphins, shared lore of this area.  Please call 
757-990-4242 to reserve your personal, intimate tour on our very plush and comfortable boat. Captain Fleming is also an Accomack County, Virginia, Marriage Celebrant.
</description>
<location>3801 Main Street (behind the Marina Bay Hotel)</location>
<phone>757-990-4242</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteaguespider.com/</website>
<lat>37.931037</lat>
<long>-75.383346</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/bLk8QUAwA172</gm_link>
</listing>

</boat-tour-listings>
