<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="xml-style.css"?>

<real-estate-company-listings>

<!-- Empty listing 
<listing>
<name categories=""></name>
<image alt="" width="320" height="">vacation-rental-companies/</image>
<description>
</description>
<location></location>
<phone></phone>
<email></email>
<website></website>
<lat></lat>
<long></long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Beach Bay Realty</name>
<image alt="Beach Bay Realty" width="250" height="68">real-estate-companies/bbr-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Beach Bay Realty "specializes in properties located between the Beach &amp; the Bay on Virginia's beautiful Eastern Shore." 
Whether you are looking to buy or sell a house, town home, condo, land, farm, or commercial property in or around Accomack 
County, including the towns of Chincoteague, Onancock, Wallops Island, Greenbackville, Temperenceville or the surrounding 
areas then you have come to the right website. Here you will find a wide array of information about local real estate for 
sale.
</description>
<location>6202 Maddox Blvd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-3600</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.beachbayrealty.com/</website>
<lat>37.936042</lat>
<long>-75.369043</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/EsLtYBoXtp72</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Coldwell Banker Harbour Realty</name>
<image alt="Coldwell Banker Harbour Realty" width="250" height="157">real-estate-companies/cb-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Whether you are in the market to buy or sell property in beautiful Chincoteague Island or Accomack County we offer over 40 years
combined real estate experience.  From purchasing a vacation home, relocating with NASA or Wallops Flight Facility to the first 
time home buyer we can help with every step. We invite you to visit our web site to search for your next Single Family Home, 
Condominium, Townhouse, Land, or Commercial real estate purchase.
</description>
<location>6455 Maddox Blvd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>800-989-5854</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.discoverchincoteague.com</website>
<lat>37.932088</lat>
<long>-75.361737</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/GUTJ1ZGfChG2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Dockside Properties</name>
<image alt="Dockside Properties" width="250" height="163">real-estate-companies/dockside-properties-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Dockside Properties, located on Chincoteague Island, has been serving the beautiful Eastern Shore of Virginia proudly for over 
15 years and now servicing Maryland as well. Here at Dockside we understand that buying or selling a home is more than just a 
transaction: it's a life-changing experience. That’s why our team of highly-seasoned real estate professionals is dedicated to 
providing exceptional, personalized service for all of our clients. We take great pride in the relationships we build and always 
work relentlessly on the client’s behalf to help them achieve their real estate goals.
</description>
<location>6325 Maddox Blvd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>888-939-SOLD</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.gowithdockside.com</website>
<lat>37.934432</lat>
<long>-75.376340</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/LFPWgvsiTf42</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Eastern Shore Properties</name>
<image alt="Eastern Shore Properties" width="250" height="188">real-estate-companies/esp-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Eastern Shore Properties can assist you with all of your property needs. We have many waterfront and non-waterfront homes, as well 
as commercial properties for sale. We can help with the entire process of buying a home - to finding the perfect lot - to assisting 
you with finding a contractor to build your "dream home" or finding a place for your new business. We also offer properties for sale 
in the surrounding areas. We are located just across from the Chincoteague Chamber of Commerce building on the traffic circle as you 
go to Assateague. 
</description>
<location>6759 Maddox Blvd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>800-515-3121</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/ESP/</website>
<lat>37.926888</lat>
<long>-75.353603</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/b8ViaKmYznw</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Keller Williams Delmarva</name>
<image alt="Keller Williams Delmarva" width="250" height="250">real-estate-companies/kwd_logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Dreaming of owning your very own piece of Paradise on the Eastern Shore of Virginia? Welcome to Keller Williams Delmarva - here to serve all of your 
Real Estate needs on beautiful Chincoteague Island &amp; beyond. We began our business with the belief that there is a better way to Buy &amp; Sell 
Homes here on the Shore. Our personal service, attention to detail, tireless attitude, &amp; knowledge of the ESVA makes us your best choice. We are also 
the leading area experts for Property Management &amp; Vacation Rentals utilizing the latest Technology in both industries! Let us help you Buy the Beach!
</description>
<location>4101 Main Street, Chincoteague, VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-7070</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://LiveTheShoreLife.com</website>
<lat>37.927764</lat>
<long>-75.355394</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Long &amp; Foster Chincoteague</name>
<image alt="Long &amp; Foster Chincoteague" width="250" height="190">real-estate-companies/Long-and-Foster-Realtors_logo.png</image>
<description>
We've been serving Chincoteague Island and the surrounding area since 1991. We provide good honest service with straight answers! Purchasing a 
home is one of the biggest decisions most people will make in their life. You want to make sure that you make a good buying decision based on 
accurate information. We know the market well and can help you navigate through the entire process, from beginning your search to closing the 
deal. 
</description>
<location>6426 Maddox Blvd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>800-668-7836</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteagueforsale.com</website>
<lat>37.932402</lat>
<long>-75.362746</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/vfH9tyQfZdK2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View">Ocean East Realty</name>
<image alt="Ocean East Realty" width="250" height="58">real-estate-companies/premierlogo.png</image>
<description>
Considering selling your property, planning to relocate, looking to purchase real estate on Chincoteague or surrounding areas of 
Virginia's Eastern Shore? Ocean East Realty is here to help. We offer hands on assistance to familiarize you with all that 
Chincoteague Island has to offer. We pride ourselves with having direct contact with each of our clients and maintaining open lines 
of communication. Our goal is to help you find that island home you've always dreamed of. Ocean East Realty is a locally owned 
company established by island natives, Linda Budd &amp; Donna Jones. Linda &amp; Donna have brought together a team of friendly professionals 
who are passionate about Chincoteague Island and all that it has to offer.
</description>
<location>6373 Maddox Blvd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>866-406-3354</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteagueoceaneast.com/</website>
<lat>37.933319</lat>
<long>-75.364055</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Seaside Properties</name>
<image alt="Seaside Properties" width="180" height="203">real-estate-companies/seaside-properties-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Whether you are in the market to buy or sell property, Seaside Properties on beautiful Chincoteague Island is here to help. We invite you to visit our 
web site to search for your next Single Family Home, Condominium, Townhouse, Land, or Commercial Real Estate purchase. Let us help you find your Happy 
Place in the Sun! We offer a full suite of Real Estate services to include Sales, Rentals, Vacation Rentals, and Property Management.  No matter what 
your Real Estate needs from Chincoteage to Captains Cove and beyond, we can fullfil all your Real Estate service needs.
</description>
<location>4073 Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6000</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://seasidepropertiesllc.com</website>
<lat>37.934190</lat>
<long>-75.377196</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/jVFb9Kich2y</gm_link>
</listing>

</real-estate-company-listings>