<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="xml-style.css"?>

<services-listings>

<!-- Empty listing 
<listing>
<name categories=""></name>
<image alt="" width="320" height="">vacation-rental-companies/</image>
<description>
</description>
<location></location>
<phone></phone>
<email></email>
<website></website>
<lat></lat>
<long></long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<listing>
<name categories="Trees Trash and Demolition">John Howard Services</name>
<image alt="John Howard Services" width="229" height="153">services/john-howard-services.jpg</image>
<description>
John Howard Services provides professional tree cutting services, including tree trimming, tree removal, and stump removal. 
We do home and business demolition. We can deliver a dumpster to your site so that you can fill it with your trash, then we will haul it 
away. John Howard Services has been in business for over 20 years and has an impeccable reputation. For a job 
<span style="font-style:italic;text-decoration:underline;">done right</span> in the Chincoteague Island area give us a call.
</description>
<location>Chincoteague VA</location>
<phone>757-336-6777</phone>
<email></email>
<website>john-howard.html</website>
<lat></lat>
<long></long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Chiropractic,Map View">Island Chiropractic Center</name>
<image alt="Island Chiropractic Center" width="220" height="220">services/Island-Chiropractic-Center.jpg</image>
<description>
Providing Chiropractic care on beautiful Chincoteague Island. We help patients get relief from back and neck pain, sciatica, 
planter fasciitis, carpal tunnel, numbness and tingling, headaches, sports injuries, pain in shoulder, wrist, hip or elbow. 
We also have a retail inventory of pain relief lotions, gels and supplements.
</description>
<location>6295 Teal Lane, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-7170</phone>
<email>islandchiropracticcenter@gmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.islandchiropractor.com</website>
<lat>37.932190</lat>
<long>-75.359869</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/df2XBgEwQvp</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Event Venues,Map View">Chincoteague Center</name>
<image alt="Chincoteague Center" width="220" height="110">services/cc-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Let world-famous Chincoteague Island be the backdrop for your next business or social event! This quaint seaside town retains the flavor of 
yesteryear while providing all the amenities of today. Whether you’re planning a convention, trade-show, corporate event or conference, class, 
festival, wedding or reunion – the Chincoteague Center provides the perfect venue and meeting place. Our modern, spacious facility can 
accommodate up to 800 attendees in a 9,000 square foot area that includes sliding wall partitions for virtually unlimited space options. Call 
or stop by for a tour of the building between 10:00 am and 3:00 pm Monday through Friday.
</description>
<location>6155 Community Drive, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-0614</phone>
<email>center@thechincoteaguecenter.com</email>
<website>https://www.thechincoteaguecenter.com/</website>
<lat>37.935738</lat>
<long>-75.359756</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/udQAS9HFaj42</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Construction">Island Homes</name>
<image alt="Island Homes" width="216" height="163">services/island-homes-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Island Homes has been established on Chincoteague Island for over 5 years. Owners Bill and Linda Melvin have lived on Chincoteague Island for many, many years
 - Bill has lived on Chincoteague Island most of his life. When it comes to quality modular, manufactured and custom-built home sales - Island Homes is your 
 first choice! Choose from many floor plans, styles and sizes from our two manufacturers - Commodore and Apex. Desire a traditional stick-built, custom home? 
 Not a problem, we design and build traditional homes as well. 
</description>
<location>, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-894-3745 | 757-894-3746 </phone>
<email>sales@islandhomesva.com</email>
<website>http://islandhomesva.com</website>
<lat>1234</lat>
<long>1234</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Home Inspections">Virginia Home Inspections</name>
<image alt="Virginia Home Inspections" width="220" height="102">services/vhi-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Virginia Home Inspections is a  locally owned inspection company with over 20 years of on the job experience in the home inspection field. Virginia 
Home Inspections has no affiliations with any other companies. We will provide you with a thorough and honest report based on what is seen on the 
day of the inspection. We are proud to serve every area of the Eastern Shore of Virginia - Chincoteague Island, Wallops Island, Atlantic, Parksley, 
Onancock and Captain's Cove in Accomack County, as well as Cape Charles, Belle Haven, and Exmore in Northampton County, just to name a few. 
</description>
<location>Grace Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-3450 or 757-894-0378</phone>
<email>info@va-homeinspections.com</email>
<website>http://www.va-homeinspections.com/</website>
<lat>1234</lat>
<long>1234</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Photography,Map View">Solid Rock Photography</name>
<image alt="Solid Rock Photography" width="220" height="275">services/srp-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
We're a highly-qualified, professional photography studio. Experienced in various types of photography, we're known for our quality. We've been 
serving the Chincoteague area for over 40 years. We take great pleasure in showcasing our style and philosophy on professional photography. We 
understand that everyone has an independent expression of who they are. Our goal is to capture the unique quality and personality of every 
individual we photograph.
</description>
<location>4395 Ridge Rd, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-3588</phone>
<email>kennylewis@verizon.net</email>
<website>http://www.solidrockphotography.com</website>
<lat>37.927712</lat>
<long>-75.368631</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/u8kZ5nG3mn72</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Power Washing">William Kambarn Power Washing</name>
<image alt="William Kambarn Power Washing" width="220" height="147">services/wkpw-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
William Kambarn Power Washing has been serving Chincoteague and the surrounding communities since 1997. William specializes in Power Washing houses, 
mobile homes, campers, decks, fences, drive ways, roofs, side walks, docks, boat bottoms and much more . William Kambarn Power Washing does residential 
and commercial work for full time residents, rental properties, STORE FRONTS, motels and prep work for many local painters . We use modern top of the 
line hot water equipment. We have on board water for those jobs where water is not available. WE POWER WASH EVERYTHING WITH HOT WATER TO LIFT AWAY DIRT, 
MOLD, GREASE AND GRIME LIKE NO OTHER AND WITHOUT DAMAGE TO THE SURFACE BEING CLEANED. 
</description>
<location>Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6886</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/wkpowerwashing/</website>
<lat>1234</lat>
<long>1234</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

</services-listings>