<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="xml-style.css"?>

<shops-listings>

<!-- Empty listing 
<listing>
<name categories=""></name>
<image alt="" width="320" height="">vacation-rental-companies/</image>
<description>
</description>
<location></location>
<phone></phone>
<email></email>
<website></website>
<lat></lat>
<long></long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">The Osprey Nest</name>
<image alt="The Osprey Nest" width="220" height="164">shops/osprey-nest-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
The Osprey Nest is Chincoteague's #1 stop for all your art needs and has been serving the community of Chincoteague and visitors for over 30 years. Our 
Art Gallery features paintings by renoun wildlife artist Kevin McBride. Our Gift Shop features a wide variety of souvenirs and gifts for all ages and 
budgets. Our exprienced custom framing department uses the materials and technology needed to preserve any type of art. 
</description>
<location>4096 Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6042</phone>
<email>kmcbride@intercom.net</email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/OspreyNest/</website>
<lat>37.934181</lat>
<long>-75.376460</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/T8jTyuJyxpD2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View,Map View">Sundial Books</name>
<image alt="Sundial Books" width="220" height="223">shops/sundial-books-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
Sundial Books is Chincoteague's locally owned year 'round full-service bookshop. Our inventory includes two floors of new, used and collectible books, 
including books about the Island and the Eastern Shore. Browse our eclectic collection of music cd's, as well as jewelry, art, gifts, journals and cards 
made by local artists. Relax in a comfortable chair and enjoy a cup of Green Mountain coffee or tea. Our goal is to make a space where our customers feel 
welcome. Check out our website for upcoming author signings, book talks, poetry readings, live music and other events. We specialize in old-fashioned 
customer service. If you can't find a book you are looking for, please let us know. We can order most books currently in print and will search our various 
resources for copies of used books.
</description>
<location>4065 Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-5825</phone>
<email>info@sundialbooks.net</email>
<website>http://www.sundialbooks.net/</website>
<lat>37.934070</lat>
<long>-75.377490</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/MMi62qpudN82</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="List View">Historic Main Street Merchants Association</name>
<image alt="Historic Main Street Merchants Association" width="220" height="265">shops/main-street-merchants-logo.jpg</image>
<description>
The Historic Main Street Merchants Association is a variety of local businesses that have come together to promote all the life and beauty that Main Street, 
Chincoteague Island has to offer. As an organization we have created some local events to promote commerce and community along with being a network for business 
communication and a channel to help local merchants work together in our beautiful island community. Our members are listed below. 
</description>
<location></location>
<phone></phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteaguemerchants.com/</website>
<lat></lat>
<long></long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

</shops-listings>