<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="xml-style.css"?>

<vacation-rental-homes-listings>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">"A Baywatch" Rentals</name>
<image alt="A Baywatch Rentals" width="250" height="162">vacation-rental-homes/baywatch-rentals.jpg</image>
<description>
Two waterfront, side-by-side rental homes in a private, quiet location face Oyster Bay on the south and a salt marsh estuary on the north.  This location is very popular with 
visitors who like to be away from traffic and near nature. The dock on Oyster Bay is quiet and relaxing, and provides simply awesome sunrises as well as crabbing and kayak 
access. Some of the famous Chincoteague Ponies graze just outside the split rail fence surrounding the yards. Geese, ducks, ospreys, shorebirds, songbirds, bunnies, and deer 
frequent the area. Wifi and gas grills are available at both houses. 
</description>
<location>Leonard Lane, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>1-888-831-0200</phone>
<email>refugeinn@verizon.net</email>
<website>http://www.refugeinn.com/baywatch/</website>
<lat>37.95784</lat>
<long>-75.33561</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/ebrcZ</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Above The Water's Edge</name>
<image alt="Above The Waters Edge" width="250" height="250">vacation-rental-homes/WatersEdge.jpg</image>
<description>
Enjoy a new construction 3 bedroom, 2.5 bath townhome with an available boat slip walking distance from downtown and steps from the water! The townhome includes a partially enclosed parking/garage area, and includes five decks, all with water views. Guest rooms include one queen, and two king beds. The location is ideal for fishing, crabbing, viewing fireworks, rocket launches, and beautiful sunsets, or simply enjoying nature from the dock. Short walking distance to the Carnival Fairgrounds. Guests are welcome to Wi-Fi and pool access. Please click on our link to learn more and see numerous photos of this well-appointed, lovely new townhome.
</description>
<location>Water's Edge Dr, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone></phone>
<email></email>
<website>https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/30686167</website>
<lat>37.930199</lat>
<long>-75.383194</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">All Season Waterfront Homes</name>
<image alt="All Season Waterfront Homes" width="250" height="183">vacation-rental-homes/allseasons.jpg</image>
<description>
These waterfront homes are located on the northeast side of Chincoteague Island. There are deep water docking facilities to moor your boat, and you can go crabbing just outside of your door. You have swimming pool privileges at Pine Grove Campground, which is within walking distance from both houses. Each house has three bedrooms and two baths. They also include central heat and air, a dishwasher, washer and dryer. Both houses have 1700 square feet of living area, a large deck cable TV, a VCR, and a stereo. Rents Saturday to Saturday only, Memorial Day to Labor Day, with a minimum of three days before Memorial Day and three days after Labor Day. 
</description>
<location>P.O. BOX 8, Chincoteague VA 23336 </location>
<phone>757-336-5200</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.allseasonshomes.com/</website>
<lat>37.93726</lat>
<long>-75.34839</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/shg62iWqDr82</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Another Day In Paradise</name>
<image alt="Another Day In Paradise" width="250" height="185">vacation-rental-homes/sip.jpg</image>
<description>
LUXURY WATERFRONT CONDO - Another Day In Paradise is a beautiful bay front condo with spectacular water views! This condo unit is in the upscale Sunset Bay Villas, located on the 
Chincoteague Bay and just a short walk from Historic Downtown Chincoteague. Includes 3 bedrooms, 2 baths, hardwood floors, granite counter tops, beautiful 
decor, and amazing water views! You can see the bay from the living room, dining room, and kitchen as well as the Master Bedroom. Amenities include a fitness 
center, a marina, a swimming pool and much, much more. Please visit our web site to discover all the features our Sunset Bay Condo offers. Come and make 
wonderful family memories at Another Day In Paradise! 
</description>
<location>Sunset Bay Villas - Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336 </location>
<phone>240-498-0074</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/AnotherDayInParadise/adip.html</website>
<lat>37.932450</lat>
<long>-75.382245</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/HHU46</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Deep Hole Creek Waterfront Vacation Rentals</name>
<image alt="Deep Hole Creek Waterfront Vacation Rentals" width="250" height="163">vacation-rental-homes/Deep-Hole-Creek-House.jpg</image>
<description>
A stunning waterfront setting combined with impeccable accommodations... Eureka!, Epiphany and Morning Song are three luxury waterfront rental houses on Deep Hole Creek overlooking Little Oyster Bay and Assateague. They all have deep water docks for swimming, boating and crabbing. They are two miles from the bridge to Assateague and the Chincoteague National Wildlife Refuge, and about a mile to the shops in town. Please see our web site for more details. 
</description>
<location>Deep Hole Road, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>703-241-7857</phone>
<email>Blair@DeepHoleCreek.com</email>
<website>http://www.deepholecreek.com/</website>
<lat>37.93887</lat>
<long>-75.34629</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/5hyFe</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Eagle's View</name>
<image alt="Eagles View" width="250" height="281">vacation-rental-homes/eagles-view.jpg</image>
<description>
Eagle's View is a luxury vacation rental overlooking the Assateague Island Channel and Lighthouse. Fully equipped for comfort and convenience, with 4 BR, 3.5 BA, Wifi, 4 flat screen TVs, DVDs, washer/dryer, upscale furnishings and a kitchen with lots of gourmet gadgets, this house is your home base for quick access to beaches, hiking trails, museums, restaurants and shops, Eastern Shore attractions, and natural beauty. Wake up to beautiful sunrises, and spend lazy days enjoying the many kinds of birds, the frequent views of the ponies, and of course the gorgeous view of the lighthouse. Enjoy fishing, crabbing or boating from the private lighted dock that is also the perfect place for stargazing. There are plenty of outdoor, waterfront living areas for family gatherings, curling up with a good book, or enjoying the cool, salt air breezes:  third floor balcony, generous deck off the great room, screened porch and dock. Come and enjoy the relaxation, peacefulness and tranquility that can be found at this gorgeous waterfront home. Beautiful sunrises, nature, and relaxation await you at Eagle's View. 
</description>
<location>7151 Sheepshead Lane, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>540-687-6923 or 757-336-1088</phone>
<email>lowelandfarm@aol.com</email>
<website>http://www.bayfronthouse.com/</website>
<lat>37.922247</lat>
<long>-75.361815</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/ryTyYDn7XkA2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Easy Does It Vacations</name>
<image alt="Easy Does It Vacations" width="250" height="167">vacation-rental-homes/edi_vacations_banner.jpg</image>
<description>
Easy Does It Vacations offers something for everyone from a single couple looking for a quiet time together to a growing family with small children, or a large family having an annual reunion. Our homes are all full size with complete kitchens, dining rooms, living rooms and plenty space to spread out the gang. All offer Wi Fi, cable TV, DVD, VCR, A/C and lots of puzzles, games, and books about the island. There are even a few bikes to explore the island. All homes also have docks for your boat or to catch a few crabs. <![CDATA[<span style="color:#FF0000;font-weight:bold;">]]>Take a Peak! Visit our Website<![CDATA[</span>. <em>]]>Check out our webcam, see what's happening on the dock.<![CDATA[</em>]]> 
</description>
<location>Various Locations, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>717-571-1765</phone>
<email>jmurphy_ediv@hotmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.easydoesitvacations.com/</website>
<lat>37.91319</lat>
<long>-75.39563</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/7ucGZ</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Grey Heron Waterfront</name>
<image alt="Grey Heron Waterfront" width="250" height="191">vacation-rental-homes/grey-heron.jpg</image>
<description>
The Grey Heron is the perfect location for your Chincoteague Island vacation. This idyllic setting offers amazing views of the Chincoteague Bay. Experience unforgettable sunsets! Direct bayfront access right from the back yard allows for clamming, crabbing, kayaking, swimming, wading and other water activities. The Grey Heron is close to nature trails and hiking. Downtown is a lovely place to experience local food, shopping and views of the bay. Ride your bicycle to the beach and throughout town. Then head downtown for dinner or use the Grey Heron’s full kitchen to cook up your catch. Dine on the covered, screened porch and watch the moon rise and the stars appear. It’s an excellent place to savor an open-air breakfast and lunch during the summer and early fall. 
</description>
<location>5123 Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>1-800-668-7836</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/GreyHeron/</website>
<lat>37.947806</lat>
<long>-75.357884</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<!--
<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Happiness House Apartment</name>
<image alt="Happiness House Apartment" width="250" height="195">vacation-rental-homes/happiness_house.jpg</image>
<description>
The large, efficiency apartment located bottom right is a quiet, separate addition to the main house. Enjoy your own private screened porch and parking. The large private dock 
may be enjoyed by the owners guests, friends and family. The shallow, sandy bottom is ideal for kayaks and canoes. Watch an endless array of birds pass by this serene natural 
wildlife setting, not to mention unparalled sunsets. Hosts, Jim and Jean Loeffert.
</description>
<location>5047 DeMarco Lane, Chincoteague Island VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6502</phone>
<email>hapihaus@verizon.net</email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/hapihaus/</website>
<lat>37.95142</lat>
<long>-75.35174</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/EhJaS</gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Holiday Cottages</name>
<image alt="Holiday Cottages" width="250" height="262">vacation-rental-homes/holiday-cottages.jpg</image>
<description>
Holiday Cottages offers a unique vacation experience on beautiful Chincoteague Island.  Our 1-bedroom &amp; 2-bedroom cottages are perfect for families with children, 
family reunions, or for a couple who want to enjoy the privacy of their own cottage. Each cottage offers a fully-equipped kitchen, dining area, &amp; living room with 
cable TV, and high-speed wireless internet.  You can park right outside your door. Grills are accessible with picnic tables provided for each cottage. Our guests also 
have access to a 24-hour linen room. Enjoy our newly renovated pool, pergola, &amp; deck for relaxing. We have tetherball &amp; corn hole, and for the kids a playground 
&amp; large sandbox. Thank You to all of our friends and guests who stay at Holiday Cottages and return year after year.  We pride ourselves on our customer service and 
family friendly atmosphere that will help ensure you have a memorable vacation experience.
</description>
<location>6113 Taylor Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6256</phone>
<email>holidaycottageschinco@gmail.com</email>
<website>http://holidaycottageschinco.com/</website>
<lat>37.937731</lat>
<long>-75.369173</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/RbknkG1gmAK2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Key West Cottages</name>
<image alt="Holiday Cottages" width="250" height="187">vacation-rental-homes/key-west-cottages.jpg</image>
<description>
Key West Cottages are nautical inspired, private waterfront accommodations with breath taking views of the Chincoteague Bay and Channel. Relax 
on the waterside balcony and breathe in the salty air!  Located in the heart of historic downtown Chincoteague Island, you will find 
restaurants, boutique shops, and the Robert Reed Wafterfront Park.  Also just minutes from the Chincoteague National Wildlife Refuge and 
pristine Assateague beaches and nature trails.  Enjoy access to a shared Indoor Pool, Hot Tub, Outdoor Pool, Fitness Center and Laundry Facility 
at the Comfort Suites next door.
</description>
<location>6125 Poplar Street W, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-3700</phone>
<email>keywestcottages@gmail.com</email>
<website>https://www.chincoteaguekeywestcottages.com/</website>
<lat>37.936775</lat>
<long>-75.373050</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/BiZthsFSeTq</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Miss Ida</name>
<image alt="Myrtle On Mumford" width="250" height="166">vacation-rental-homes/miss-ida.jpg</image>
<description>
Miss Ida is brand new construction, yet she evokes Chincoteague of yesteryear. A stunning blend of modern amenities and traditional styling provides
extraordinary and luxurious comfort for guests. Full linen service and soap products, all of exceptional quality, are provided. The traditional Chincoteague 
1920's architecture of Miss Ida, along with the wonderful antique furnishings and decor will transport you back to a bygone era.
The queen bedroom has a private half bath. The second bedroom with two twins is adjacent to a full hallway bath. Rear screened porch or front porch...
great outdoor space at this unique Chincoteague home. For larger groups, this house can also be rented with neighboring Myrtle on Mumford.
</description>
<location>6334 Mumford Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-1236</phone>
<email></email>
<website>https://igetaway.net/missida.php</website>
<lat>37.937731</lat>
<long>-75.369173</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/LGoYH8aWG9t</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Moorings North</name>
<image alt="Moorings North" width="250" height="166">vacation-rental-homes/moorings-north.jpg</image>
<description>
Experience sunsets you’ll never forget! Watch the sun come down from the panoramic wall of windows in the great room, from two private balconies off of two spacious identical master suites, from the Gazebo-In-The-Sky, or the bulkheaded waterfront in your backyard. The elegant ambiance of this upscale estate will provide any amenities you are wishing for plus more. Ten guests sleep comfortably in three king size, and four twin size beds. Moorings North is designed to easily accommodate bigger families as well as to offer a tranquil setting for a romantic getaway. Enjoy many of the wonderful attractions Chincoteague has to offer while pamper yourself in a vacation home you are cordially welcome and promised to enjoy your vacation time to the fullest.
</description>
<location>4411 Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>610-458-2460</phone>
<email>Claudia@MooringsNorth.com</email>
<website>https://mooringsnorth.com/</website>
<lat>37.939937</lat>
<long>-75.368964</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/jmJTNqD1EDo</gm_link>
</listing>

<!--
<listing>
<name categories="Map View">My Island Escape</name>
<image alt="Myrtle On Mumford" width="250" height="197">vacation-rental-homes/my-island-escape.jpg</image>
<description>
Large, brand new, 3 bedroom, 2 1/2 bath home with lots of room and privacy for every family member!  Located  in a quiet neighborhood just minutes from downtown.  This new home is modern and spacious.  Enjoy water view and use of private dock where you will find cooling breezes, natures wonder, and passing birds.  Every evening, Mother Nature creates an original masterpiece of her endless sunsets, making for a great photo opt!
</description>
<location> 5061 Demarco Lane, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6502</phone>
<email>hapihaus@verizon.net</email>
<website>https://chincoteagueislandrental.com/</website>
<lat>37.951315</lat>
<long>-75.351829</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/uPyHiq8qeSC2</gm_link>
</listing>
-->

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Myrtle On Mumford</name>
<image alt="Myrtle On Mumford" width="250" height="166">vacation-rental-homes/myrtle-on-mumford.jpg</image>
<description>
Myrtle on Mumford is a newly-constructed home that combines character and charm, reminiscent of Chincoteague Island life a century ago, with the upscale finishings, furnishings, and amenities of today. The home features two bedrooms, one bath, a dining area with seating for six, a living room, a contemporary gourmet kitchen, and central heat and air conditioning. The house is located in the downtown Main Street historic area, less than a five minute walk from town. Myrtle on Mumford is the perfect home for your Chincoteague Island getaway. We invite you to explore our web site. You will be pleasantly surprised!
</description>
<location>6330 Mumford Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-1236</phone>
<email></email>
<website>https://igetaway.net/myrtleonmumford.php</website>
<lat>37.937731</lat>
<long>-75.369173</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/LGoYH8aWG9t</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Salty Dog's Lair</name>
<image alt="Salty Dogs Lair" width="250" height="188">vacation-rental-homes/saltydogs.jpg</image>
<description>
Lovingly restored 3 bedroom, 2.5 bath older home, "in town" on the Island, near the old firehouse and the harbor. Walk to restaurants, shops, library, town dock, boat ramp, grocery store, and historic area on Main Street. Across the street from Muller's Ice Cream and the Hot Stuff shop. Just a ten minute drive to Assateague Island and the ponies!
</description>
<location>6284 Cropper Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone></phone>
<email>kevingregg@gmail.com</email>
<website>http://www.vrbo.com/384053</website>
<lat>37.93308</lat>
<long>-75.37793</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/9nQcQ</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Sea Gate</name>
<image alt="Sea Gate" width="250">vacation-rental-homes/sea-gate.jpg</image>
<description>
Relax and unwind at one of the most beautiful waterfront townhomes
overlooking the Chincoteague Channel. With the living room and master
bedroom balconies overlooking the Chincoteague Channel, you will take in
some of the most peaceful sights Chincoteague has to offer. Every room boast
a relaxing water view, with the ability to view both the sunrise and sunset.
When you stay here you will really say "life is better on the water."
</description>
<location>Marsh Island Dr, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>(757)336-1088 or (757)894-3009 cell</phone>
<email>pattjack1@verizon.net</email>
<website>https://www.chincoteague.com/Sea-Gate/</website>
<lat>37.935686</lat>
<long>-75.378786</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Sea Shell Cottages</name>
<image alt="Sea Shell Cottages" width="250" height="188">vacation-rental-homes/sea-shell-cottages.jpg</image>
<description>
We have many cottages to offer from one bedroom cottages to three bedroom Chincoteague style homes. All the cottages are within walking distance to town and the carnival grounds. Off the beaten track, these homes offer convenience, privacy and quiet relaxation. Plus pool privledges at Sea Shell Motel.
</description>
<location>3720 Willow Street, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-6589</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.seashellmotel.org/accommodations/chris-cottage.php</website>
<lat>37.93111</lat>
<long>-75.37478</long>
<gm_link>https://goo.gl/maps/iRfnVaaM6fN2</gm_link>
</listing>

<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Steve's Cottages</name>
<image alt="Sea Shell Cottages" width="250" height="176">vacation-rental-homes/steves-cottages.jpg</image>
<description>
Looking for an affordable Chincoteague Island vacation? Need more space than a hotel room? Steve's Cottages is what you've been looking for! Steve's Cottages are located on a quiet side street within walking distance to the historic downtown area and just one block away from the restaurants and attractions on Maddox Blvd. After a long day at the beach relax in our pool! 
</description>
<location>6167 Taylor St, Chincoteague VA 23336</location>
<phone>757-336-7070
</phone>
<email></email>
<website>https://www.seasidevacations.rentals/community/steves-cottages</website>
<lat>37.936760</lat>
<long>-75.367636</long>
<gm_link></gm_link>
</listing>

<!--
<listing>
<name categories="Map View">Sunset In Paradise</name>
<image alt="Another Day In Paradise" width="250" height="188">vacation-rental-homes/sip.jpg</image>
<description>
LUXURY WATERFRONT CONDO - Sunset In Paradise is a beautiful bay front condo with spectacular water views! This condo unit is in the upscale Sunset Bay Villas, located on the 
Chincoteague Bay and just a short walk from Historic Downtown Chincoteague. Includes 3 bedrooms, 2 baths, hardwood floors, granite counter tops, beautiful 
decor, and amazing water views! You can see the bay from the living room, dining room, and kitchen as well as the Master Bedroom. Amenities include a fitness 
center, a marina, a swimming pool and much, much more. Please visit our web site to discover all the features our Sunset Bay Condo offers. Come and make 
wonderful family memories at Sunset In Paradise! 
</description>
<location>Sunset Bay Villas - Main Street, Chincoteague VA 23336 </location>
<phone>240-498-0074</phone>
<email></email>
<website>http://www.chincoteague.com/AnotherDayInParadise/sip.html</website>
<lat>37.932715</lat>
<long>-75.381298</long>
<gm_link>http://goo.gl/maps/HHU46</gm_link>
</listing>
-->

</vacation-rental-homes-listings>